<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>Ontext Sensitive Help (CSH) for table tx_generic_domain_model_address</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
        <csh_table>tx_generic_domain_model_address</csh_table>
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="free_text_address.description">Container for free text address elements</label>
			<label index="country.description">Country details</label>
			<label index="administrative_area.description">Details of the top-level area division in the country, such as state, district, province, island, region, etc. Note that some countries do not have this</label>
			<label index="sub_administrative_area.description">The next level down division of the area. E.g. state / county, province / reservation. Note that not all countries have a subadministrative area</label>
			<label index="locality.description">Details of Locality which is a named densely populated area  (a place) such as town, village, suburb, etc. A locality composes of many individual addresses.  Many localities exist in an administrative area or a sub adminisrative area. A locality can also have sub localities. For example, a municipality locality can have many villages associated with it which are sub localities. Example: Tamil Nadu State, Erode District, Bhavani Taluk, Paruvachi Village is a valid address in India. Tamil Nadu is the Administrative Area, Erode is the sub admin area, Bhavani is the locality, and Paruvachi is the sub locality</label>
			<label index="thoroughfare.description">Details of the Access route along which buildings/lot/land are located, such as street, road, channel, crescent, avenue, etc. This also includes canals/banks on which houses/boat houses are located where people live</label>
			<label index="premises.description">Details of the Premises (could be building(s), site, loaction, property, premise, place) which is a landmark place which has a main address such as large mail user (e.g. Airport, Hospital, University) or could be a building (e.g. apartment, house)  or a building or complex of buildings (e.g. an apartment complex or shopping centre) or even a vacant land (e.g. LOT). A premises can have many sub-addresses such as apartments in a building having its own addresses or buildings within an airport having its own addresses including its own thoroughfares</label>
			<label index="post_code.description">A container for a single free text or structured postcode. Note that not all countries have post codes</label>
			<label index="rural_delivery.description">A container for postal-specific delivery identifier for remote communities. Note that not all countries have RuralDelivery</label>
			<label index="postal_delivery_point.description">Final mail delivery point where the mail is dropped off for recipients to pick them up directly. E.g. POBox, Private Bag,  pigeon hole, free mail numbers, etc.</label>
			<label index="post_office.description">A delivery point/installation where all mails are delivered and the post man/delivery service picks up the mails and delivers it to the recipients through a delivery mode. Examples are a rural post office where post is delivered, a post office containing post office boxes/personal mail boxes. Note that not all countries have PostOffice. Can be used to represent overseas military addresses also along with PostalDeliveryPoint element</label>
			<label index="type.description">Defines the type of address. An address type can be" Primary Address, Secondary Address, Rural Address, Military Address, etc.</label>
			<label index="address_id.description">A unique address identifier such as postal delivery idetifier assigned to the address by local postal authority, e.g. DPID in Australia</label>
			<label index="address_id_type.description">Type of address ID used. e.g. DPID, etc.</label>
			<label index="tx_generic_usage.description">The purpose the address is used for. E.g.  Postal, residential, business,  exchange, update, create, delete, etc</label>
			<label index="delivery_mode.description">Mode of delivery of address. For example: rural route, normal delivery, post office box, etc.</label>
			<label index="status.description">Status of the entity. e.g. Old, Current, Inactive, Active, etc.</label>
		</languageKey>
    </data>
</T3locallang>